

THANH NGUYEN

UI/UX Design

Contact information

May 02, 1998

0332528555

thanhthanh2718@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://bit.ly/44dNP8A

HCM, Vietnam

Female

Objective

A passionate self-taught UI/UX Designer with a curious mind who loves finding and solving problems. Creating functional and enjoyable digital experiences that are valuable to the business and leave a positive impact on people is what I'm passionate about.

Skills

Language:

English Basic.

Computer:

Word, Excel, PowerPoints, Power BI, Power Query, Canva, Illustrator Basic, Photoshop Basic, Lightroom, and Figma, HTML, CSS.

Interests

I like to draw, travel, explore, and learn new things.

Education

DNU UNIVERSITY | OCT 2016 - DEC 2020

Major: Accounting

MINDX TECHNOLOGY SCHOOL | APR 2023 - NOV 2023

Major: User Interface & User Experience Design Intensive

I have experience in several mobile application projects including personal projects and projects during my studies. During my studies, I learned to pay attention to customer's problems and needs, learn about the user's target audience, and build designs in the most creative and appropriate way.

COURSERA | NOV 2023 - APR 2024

Major: Google UX Design Professional Certificate

I self-study with passion and improve my knowledge and skills. Creating functional and enjoyable digital experiences.

Work experience

C.P Vietnam Corporation | March 2022 - Present

Accountant

Main responsibilities:

Control and manage Fresh Shop wholesale and retail stores across the country.

Record and send data to achieve product transparency.

Measure and calculate product costs.

Track inventory transactions.

Support, improve, and maintain internal control related to inventory.

Understand and use SAP accounting software.

Attend the Power BI Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

Participate in guiding and training team members on power BI knowledge.

Design report data using learned knowledge.

Write CSS files to support reports for the team.

Create UI for mobile reports.

Hai Nam Thinh. Ltd Liability Company. | Aug 2020 - Feb 2022

Secretary - Design Engineer

Check the quantity of materials and the unit price of equipment. Prepare and sign contracts with customers.

Prepare documents and payment procedures.

Arrange and store records according to the company's general procedures and regulations.

Write documents and dispatches as required.

Participate in bidding and prepare project estimates.

design drawings through AutoCAD software.

quoting project prices for customers.

Calculate salaries for officers and employees.

Plan, report progress, and update new policy changes for employees.

Perform other related tasks according to the guidance of the Board of Directors.

Prepare weekly reports, monthly reports, and incident reports.

Achievements and skills gained:
Observe, learn and design construction drawings
Improve customer communication skills and work organization skills.

Activities

DNU: SPRING VOLUNTEER 2018 | FEB 2018 - MAR 2018 Volunteer team member.

Make and assemble gifts for the homeless. Share and encourage people to overcome difficulties and have optimistic thoughts.

Honors & Awards

2023: I am a member of the group that continuously ranks first and second at the UI/UX Design of Mindx courses.

Certifications

2018: Certificate in basic and advanced information technology applications

2019: TOEIC Certificate of Achievenment 490+

2020: DNU University Certificate

2023: UI/UX Intensive Certificate of Mindx Technology School

2023: Google UX Design Certificate